[{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Throughput?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Error_Rate?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Jitter?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Latency?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Interplay_Factors?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Bandwidth?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"bw","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Congession?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Computer_Networks?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"sec","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"scope","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"n1","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Security?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"availabilty","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"modi","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"confid","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"integ","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"interrr","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"sec","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Scope?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"s1","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"s2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"s3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"s4","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"scope","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"NCP is a subClass from Session","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"ISO_Standard is a subClass from Session","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Media_Access_Control_Sublayer is a subClass from Data_Link","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Presentation is a subClass from Data_Link","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Fully_Connected is a subClass from Mesh","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Hybrid is a subClass from Mesh","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"both a and b ","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":" none of them is true ","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Silicon_Photo_Diode is a subClass from Infrared","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Satellites is a subClass from Infrared","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"both a and b ","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":" none of them is true ","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"SNTP is a subClass from NTP","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"NetBIOS is a subClass from NTP","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"both a and b ","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":" none of them is true ","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Negative_Filter is a subClass from Packet_Fittering_Routers","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Single_Homed_Bastion is a subClass from Packet_Fittering_Routers","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"BASET is a subClass from Gigabit_Ethernet","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"CD is a subClass from Gigabit_Ethernet","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"IAX is a subClass from VOIP","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"eMail is a subClass from VOIP","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Extreme_Network is a subClass from ExtremeXOS","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"ZyNOS is a subClass from ExtremeXOS","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"both a and b ","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":" none of them is true ","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Pure_Honeypots is a subClass from Honeypots","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Rule_Based_Detection is a subClass from Honeypots","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Variable_Bit_Rate is a subClass from ","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Type_5 is a subClass from ","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"both a and b ","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":" none of them is true ","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"STS-1 is a subClass from SDH","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Internet_Protocol is a subClass from SDH","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"both a and b ","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":" none of them is true ","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Extranet is a subClass from Scope","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Protocol is a subClass from Scope","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Application_Layer is a subClass from IP_Suite","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Topology is a subClass from IP_Suite","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Firewall is a subClass from System_Security","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Fabrication is a subClass from System_Security","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Spammer_Programs is a subClass from Malicious_Software","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Passive_Attacks is a subClass from Malicious_Software","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Class_F is a subClass from Shielded_Foiled_Twisted_Pair","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Bonded_TP is a subClass from Shielded_Foiled_Twisted_Pair","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Active_Hub is a subClass from Hub","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Modem is a subClass from Hub","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Routing_table is a subClass from Router","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Repeater is a subClass from Router","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Socket_Address is a subClass from Transport_Layer","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Network_Interface is a subClass from Transport_Layer","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"both a and b ","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":" none of them is true ","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which one of the following response pairs are related ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Application\tuses\tRADIUS","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Network\tuses\tRADIUS","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"ISO_Standard\tuses\tRADIUS","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Data_Link\tuses\tRADIUS","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which one of the following response pairs are related ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Internet_Society\tcommittee\tIAB","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"eMail\tcommittee\tIAB","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"VOIP\tcommittee\tIAB","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"RFC\tcommittee\tIAB","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"property"}]